Guide to the Alexander Hamilton Papers Publication Project records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VII: Microfilms
  - Subseries VII.3: Documents from the National Archives
    - Claim of M. de Beaumarchais; Records of the Boundary and Claims Commissions & Arbitrations filled with French Spoilation Records (Box 318)
    - Notes from the British Legation in the US to the Department of State, 26 Oct 1791-15 Aug 1794 (Box 318)
    - Letters sent by the Commissioner of Revenue (Box 318)
    - Papers of the Continental Congress: Item 87, Letters from Thomas Jefferson (Box 319)
    - Papers of the Continental Congress: Items 1870191: Acts of Federal Congress (Box 319)
    - Diplomatic and Consular Instructions of the Department of State, 23 Jan 1791-1 June 1795 (Box 319)
    - Domestic Letters of the Department of State, 4 Feb 1792-12 Oct 1795 (Box 319)
    - Foreign Letters of the Continental Congress & Department of State, 14 Jan 1785-23 Dec 1790 (Box 319)
    - Miscellaneous Letters of the Department of State, 1 Jan 1793-31 Dec 1794 (Box 319)
    - Despatches from Special Agents of the Department of State, 3 April 1794-30 Oct 1811 (Box 319)
    - Notes from the French Legation in the US to the Department of State, 7 June 1789-1 March 1805 (Box 319)
    - Alexander Hamilton Documents in the Library of Congress (Box 319)
    - Alexander Hamilton Documents in the National Archive (Box 319)
    - Correspondence of the Secretary of the Treasury with the Collectors of Customs, 1789-1833 (Box 320)
    - Notes from the Spanish Legation in the US to the Department of State, 26 Feb 1790-16 Aug 1794 (Box 320)
    - State Department Territorial Papers: Territory Northwest of the River Ohio, 1797-1801 (Box 320)
    - State Department Territorial Papers: Territory Southwest of the River Ohio, 1790-1795 (Box 320)
    - Minutes of the Supreme Court of the US, 1 Feb 1790-4 Aug 1828 (Box 320)
    - Register of Audits of Miscellaneous Treasury Accounts, March 1790-March 1814 (Box 320)
    - Despatches from US Ministers to France, 16 Jan 1791-6 Aug 1792 (Box 320)
    - Despatches from US Ministers to Great Britain, 29 Nov 1791-4 May 1797 (Box 320)
    - Correspondence on Naval Affairs - War Department, 1790-1798 (Box 320)
- Series VIII. Card File Indexes
  - Main File (1-4700) (Box Drawer 1, Folder File 1)
  - Main File (4800-9500) (Box Drawer 1, Folder File 2)
  - Main File (9600-14400) (Box Drawer 2, Folder File 1)
  - Main File (14500-19000) (Box Drawer 2, Folder File 2)
  - Supplementary vol. (1774-1863); (Canada-Wisconsin) (Box Drawer 3, Folder File 1)
  - Manuscript Sources - Ms. Citation (A-Y); Misc. Citation (A-Z); Updated dealers quotes, Dealers (Box Drawer 3, Folder File 1)
  - Books (A-Z) (Box Drawer 3, Folder File 1)
  - Treasury Dept. - Circular, 1789-1794 (Box Drawer 3, Folder File 1)
  - Treasury Dept. - Register of the Treasury, 1789-1795 (Box Drawer 3, Folder File 1)
  - Treasury Dept. - MA Loan Office, 1789-1791 (Box Drawer 3, Folder File 1)
  - Treasury Dept. - PA Loan Office, 1791-1795 (Box Drawer 3, Folder File 1)
  - Hamilton (A-Z) (Box Drawer 3, Folder File 2)
  - Neither/Nor (A-Z) (Box Drawer 4, Folder File 1)